4:20 • 24/7 • 30 Days
Super High Me is a documentary, comedy film directed by Michael Blieden.
Determined to find out the true effects of marijuana on the human body, stand-up comedian and former Stoner of the Year Doug
Benson documents his experience avoiding pot for 30 days and then consuming massive amounts of the drug for 30 days.
More than just an amusing story of one man's quest to get superhigh, this documentary
also examines the hotly contested debate over medical marijuana use.
Self, played by Doug Benson.
Self, played by Sarah Silverman.
Self, played by Patton Oswalt.
Self, played by Jeff Ross.
Self, played by Gary Cohan.
Self, played by Robert Gore.
Super High Me is a 2007 documentary film about the
effects of smoking cannabis for 30 days.
Directed by Michael Blieden, the documentary stars comedian Doug Benson.
The documentary's name and its poster are plays on
the 2004 documentary Super Size Me.
The tone is lighthearted.